<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<?metadataRepository version='1.1.0'?>
<repository name='file:/C:/MyBatis/generator/eclipse/UpdateSite/ - metadata' type='org.eclipse.equinox.internal.p2.metadata.repository.LocalMetadataRepository' version='1.0.0'>
  <properties size='2'>
    <property name='p2.timestamp' value='1342466522948'/>
    <property name='p2.compressed' value='false'/>
  </properties>
  <references size='2'>
    <repository uri='http://mybatis.googlecode.com/svn/sub-projects/generator/trunk/eclipse/UpdateSite' url='http://mybatis.googlecode.com/svn/sub-projects/generator/trunk/eclipse/UpdateSite' type='1' options='0'/>
    <repository uri='http://mybatis.googlecode.com/svn/sub-projects/generator/trunk/eclipse/UpdateSite' url='http://mybatis.googlecode.com/svn/sub-projects/generator/trunk/eclipse/UpdateSite' type='0' options='0'/>
  </references>
  <units size='24'>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' version='1.3.2.201207161521'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Core'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='35'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.ant' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.java' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.xml' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.templates' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.model' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.annotated' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.sqlprovider' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.model' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.config' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.config.xml' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.exception' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.db' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.rules' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.types' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.util' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.util.messages' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.logging' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.plugins' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.ant' range='1.7.1' optional='true'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.log4j' range='1.2.15' optional='true'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Name: MyBatis Generator Core&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Require-Bundle: org.apache.ant;bundle-version=&quot;1.7.1&quot;;resolution:=optional,org.apache.log4j;bundle-version=&quot;1.2.15&quot;;resolution:=optional&#xA;Export-Package: org.mybatis.generator.ant,org.mybatis.generator.api,org.mybatis.generator.api.dom,org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.java,org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.xml,org.mybatis.generator.codegen,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.elements,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.templates,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.model,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap.elements,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.annotated,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.sqlprovider,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.model,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper,org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper.elements,org.mybatis.generator.config,org.mybatis.generator.config.xml,org.mybatis.generator.exception,org.mybatis.generator.internal,org.mybatis.generator.internal.db,org.mybatis.generator.internal.rules,org.mybatis.generator.internal.types,org.mybatis.generator.internal.util,org.mybatis.generator.internal.util.messages,org.mybatis.generator.logging,org.mybatis.generator.plugins&#xA;Bundle-RequiredExecutionEnvironment: J2SE-1.5&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.core&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-Vendor: mybatis.org
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='6'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Eclipse Core Support'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='5'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.callback' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.merge' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='5'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.core' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jface.text' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.6.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Name: MyBatis Generator Eclipse Core Support&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Require-Bundle: org.mybatis.generator.core;bundle-version=&quot;1.3.0&quot;,org.eclipse.jdt.core;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.jface.text;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.core.resources;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.core.runtime;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;&#xA;Export-Package: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.callback,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.merge&#xA;Bundle-RequiredExecutionEnvironment: J2SE-1.5&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-Vendor: mybatis.org
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator Core Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.core.source&#xA;Bundle-Name: %pluginName&#xA;Bundle-Localization: plugin&#xA;Eclipse-SourceBundle: org.mybatis.generator.core;version=&quot;1.3.1.201101032122&quot;;roots:=&quot;.&quot;&#xA;Bundle-Vendor: %providerName
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' version='1.3.2.201207161521'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator Source Feature'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.mybatis.generator.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.mybatis.generator.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' version='1.3.1.201101032122'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator Source Feature'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.mybatis.generator.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.mybatis.generator.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.2.201207161521'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator UI Plugin'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='8'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.actions' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.ant' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.buildpath' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.content' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.wizards' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='10'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.ant' range='1.7.1'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ant.core' range='3.2.200'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.core' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ui.ide' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.ui' range='3.6.1'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator UI Plugin Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Core'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='35'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.ant' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.java' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.api.dom.xml' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.dao.templates' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.model' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.ibatis2.sqlmap.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.annotated' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.javamapper.elements.sqlprovider' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.model' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.codegen.mybatis3.xmlmapper.elements' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.config' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.config.xml' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.exception' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.db' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.rules' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.types' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.util' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.internal.util.messages' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.logging' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.plugins' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.ant' range='1.7.1' optional='true'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.log4j' range='1.2.15' optional='true'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.core&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator Source Feature'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='4'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.2.201207161521'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Documentation'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator UI Plugin Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source&#xA;Bundle-Name: %pluginName&#xA;Bundle-Localization: plugin&#xA;Eclipse-SourceBundle: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui;version=&quot;1.3.1.201101032122&quot;;roots:=&quot;.,lib/antsupportsrc&quot;&#xA;Bundle-Vendor: %providerName
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.0.0.47A3cLi26h7E7AA7A7IEAEE'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.0.0.47A3cLi26h7E7AA7A7IEAEE'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='2'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.1.201101032122'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Documentation'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-Vendor: mybatis.org&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Name: MyBatis Generator Documentation&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator Source Feature'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.&#xA;'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.&#xA;'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='4'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.source' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.jar' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' version='1.3.1.201101032122'>
      <properties size='8'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='3'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='feature' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.update.feature' name='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </provides>
      <filter>
        (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
      </filter>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='org.eclipse.update.feature' id='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='zipped'>
            true
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.0.0.787M7AcLi26h7UEMQEkIoQcUQ'>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.category' value='true'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='1'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator' version='1.0.0.787M7AcLi26h7UEMQEkIoQcUQ'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='4'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' range='[1.3.2.201207161521,1.3.2.201207161521]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator Core Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.core.source&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.1.201101032122'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator UI Plugin'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='8'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.actions' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.ant' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.buildpath' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.content' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.wizards' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='10'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ui' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='0.0.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.apache.ant' range='1.7.1'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ant.core' range='3.2.200'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.core' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.ui.ide' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.ui' range='3.6.1'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-Vendor: mybatis.org&#xA;Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Activator: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.Activator&#xA;Bundle-RequiredExecutionEnvironment: J2SE-1.5&#xA;Require-Bundle: org.eclipse.ui,org.eclipse.core.runtime,org.apache.ant;bundle-version=&quot;1.7.1&quot;,org.mybatis.generator.core;bundle-version=&quot;1.3.0&quot;,org.eclipse.ant.core;bundle-version=&quot;3.2.200&quot;,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core;bundle-version=&quot;1.3.0&quot;,org.eclipse.jdt.core;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.core.resources;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.ui.ide;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.0&quot;,org.eclipse.jdt.ui;bundle-version=&quot;3.6.1&quot;&#xA;Bundle-Name: MyBatis Generator UI Plugin&#xA;Bundle-ActivationPolicy: lazy&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui;singleton:=true&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Export-Package: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.actions,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.ant,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.buildpath,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.content,org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui.wizards
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='9'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%featureName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.description' value='%description'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.type.group' value='true'/>
        <property name='df_LT.featureName' value='MyBatis Generator'/>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.description' value='MyBatis Generator - a code generator for MyBatis/iBATIS'/>
        <property name='df_LT.copyright' value='Copyright 2010 Jeff Butler&#xA;Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the &quot;License&quot;);&#xA;you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.&#xA;You may obtain a copy of the License at&#xA;&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0&#xA;&#xA;Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software&#xA;distributed under the License is distributed on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.&#xA;See the License for the specific language governing permissions and&#xA;limitations under the License.'/>
        <property name='df_LT.license' value='Apache License&#xA;Version 2.0, January 2004&#xA;http://www.apache.org/licenses/&#xA;&#xA;TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION, AND DISTRIBUTION&#xA;&#xA;1. Definitions.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;License&quot; shall mean the terms and conditions for use, reproduction,&#xA;and distribution as defined by Sections 1 through 9 of this document.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Licensor&quot; shall mean the copyright owner or entity authorized by&#xA;the copyright owner that is granting the License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Legal Entity&quot; shall mean the union of the acting entity and all&#xA;other entities that control, are controlled by, or are under common&#xA;control with that entity. For the purposes of this definition,&#xA;&quot;control&quot; means (i) the power, direct or indirect, to cause the&#xA;direction or management of such entity, whether by contract or&#xA;otherwise, or (ii) ownership of fifty percent (50%) or more of the&#xA;outstanding shares, or (iii) beneficial ownership of such entity.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;You&quot; (or &quot;Your&quot;) shall mean an individual or Legal Entity&#xA;exercising permissions granted by this License.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Source&quot; form shall mean the preferred form for making modifications,&#xA;including but not limited to software source code, documentation&#xA;source, and configuration files.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Object&quot; form shall mean any form resulting from mechanical&#xA;transformation or translation of a Source form, including but&#xA;not limited to compiled object code, generated documentation,&#xA;and conversions to other media types.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Work&quot; shall mean the work of authorship, whether in Source or&#xA;Object form, made available under the License, as indicated by a&#xA;copyright notice that is included in or attached to the work&#xA;(an example is provided in the Appendix below).&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Derivative Works&quot; shall mean any work, whether in Source or Object&#xA;form, that is based on (or derived from) the Work and for which the&#xA;editorial revisions, annotations, elaborations, or other modifications&#xA;represent, as a whole, an original work of authorship. For the purposes&#xA;of this License, Derivative Works shall not include works that remain&#xA;separable from, or merely link (or bind by name) to the interfaces of,&#xA;the Work and Derivative Works thereof.&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contribution&quot; shall mean any work of authorship, including&#xA;the original version of the Work and any modifications or additions&#xA;to that Work or Derivative Works thereof, that is intentionally&#xA;submitted to Licensor for inclusion in the Work by the copyright owner&#xA;or by an individual or Legal Entity authorized to submit on behalf of&#xA;the copyright owner. For the purposes of this definition, &quot;submitted&quot;&#xA;means any form of electronic, verbal, or written communication sent&#xA;to the Licensor or its representatives, including but not limited to&#xA;communication on electronic mailing lists, source code control systems,&#xA;and issue tracking systems that are managed by, or on behalf of, the&#xA;Licensor for the purpose of discussing and improving the Work, but&#xA;excluding communication that is conspicuously marked or otherwise&#xA;designated in writing by the copyright owner as &quot;Not a Contribution.&quot;&#xA;&#xA;&quot;Contributor&quot; shall mean Licensor and any individual or Legal Entity&#xA;on behalf of whom a Contribution has been received by Licensor and&#xA;subsequently incorporated within the Work.&#xA;&#xA;2. Grant of Copyright License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;copyright license to reproduce, prepare Derivative Works of,&#xA;publicly display, publicly perform, sublicense, and distribute the&#xA;Work and such Derivative Works in Source or Object form.&#xA;&#xA;3. Grant of Patent License. Subject to the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, each Contributor hereby grants to You a perpetual,&#xA;worldwide, non-exclusive, no-charge, royalty-free, irrevocable&#xA;(except as stated in this section) patent license to make, have made,&#xA;use, offer to sell, sell, import, and otherwise transfer the Work,&#xA;where such license applies only to those patent claims licensable&#xA;by such Contributor that are necessarily infringed by their&#xA;Contribution(s) alone or by combination of their Contribution(s)&#xA;with the Work to which such Contribution(s) was submitted. If You&#xA;institute patent litigation against any entity (including a&#xA;cross-claim or counterclaim in a lawsuit) alleging that the Work&#xA;or a Contribution incorporated within the Work constitutes direct&#xA;or contributory patent infringement, then any patent licenses&#xA;granted to You under this License for that Work shall terminate&#xA;as of the date such litigation is filed.&#xA;&#xA;4. Redistribution. You may reproduce and distribute copies of the&#xA;Work or Derivative Works thereof in any medium, with or without&#xA;modifications, and in Source or Object form, provided that You&#xA;meet the following conditions:&#xA;&#xA;(a) You must give any other recipients of the Work or&#xA;Derivative Works a copy of this License; and&#xA;&#xA;(b) You must cause any modified files to carry prominent notices&#xA;stating that You changed the files; and&#xA;&#xA;(c) You must retain, in the Source form of any Derivative Works&#xA;that You distribute, all copyright, patent, trademark, and&#xA;attribution notices from the Source form of the Work,&#xA;excluding those notices that do not pertain to any part of&#xA;the Derivative Works; and&#xA;&#xA;(d) If the Work includes a &quot;NOTICE&quot; text file as part of its&#xA;distribution, then any Derivative Works that You distribute must&#xA;include a readable copy of the attribution notices contained&#xA;within such NOTICE file, excluding those notices that do not&#xA;pertain to any part of the Derivative Works, in at least one&#xA;of the following places: within a NOTICE text file distributed&#xA;as part of the Derivative Works; within the Source form or&#xA;documentation, if provided along with the Derivative Works; or,&#xA;within a display generated by the Derivative Works, if and&#xA;wherever such third-party notices normally appear. The contents&#xA;of the NOTICE file are for informational purposes only and&#xA;do not modify the License. You may add Your own attribution&#xA;notices within Derivative Works that You distribute, alongside&#xA;or as an addendum to the NOTICE text from the Work, provided&#xA;that such additional attribution notices cannot be construed&#xA;as modifying the License.&#xA;&#xA;You may add Your own copyright statement to Your modifications and&#xA;may provide additional or different license terms and conditions&#xA;for use, reproduction, or distribution of Your modifications, or&#xA;for any such Derivative Works as a whole, provided Your use,&#xA;reproduction, and distribution of the Work otherwise complies with&#xA;the conditions stated in this License.&#xA;&#xA;5. Submission of Contributions. Unless You explicitly state otherwise,&#xA;any Contribution intentionally submitted for inclusion in the Work&#xA;by You to the Licensor shall be under the terms and conditions of&#xA;this License, without any additional terms or conditions.&#xA;Notwithstanding the above, nothing herein shall supersede or modify&#xA;the terms of any separate license agreement you may have executed&#xA;with Licensor regarding such Contributions.&#xA;&#xA;6. Trademarks. This License does not grant permission to use the trade&#xA;names, trademarks, service marks, or product names of the Licensor,&#xA;except as required for reasonable and customary use in describing the&#xA;origin of the Work and reproducing the content of the NOTICE file.&#xA;&#xA;7. Disclaimer of Warranty. Unless required by applicable law or&#xA;agreed to in writing, Licensor provides the Work (and each&#xA;Contributor provides its Contributions) on an &quot;AS IS&quot; BASIS,&#xA;WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or&#xA;implied, including, without limitation, any warranties or conditions&#xA;of TITLE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY, or FITNESS FOR A&#xA;PARTICULAR PURPOSE. You are solely responsible for determining the&#xA;appropriateness of using or redistributing the Work and assume any&#xA;risks associated with Your exercise of permissions under this License.&#xA;&#xA;8. Limitation of Liability. In no event and under no legal theory,&#xA;whether in tort (including negligence), contract, or otherwise,&#xA;unless required by applicable law (such as deliberate and grossly&#xA;negligent acts) or agreed to in writing, shall any Contributor be&#xA;liable to You for damages, including any direct, indirect, special,&#xA;incidental, or consequential damages of any character arising as a&#xA;result of this License or out of the use or inability to use the&#xA;Work (including but not limited to damages for loss of goodwill,&#xA;work stoppage, computer failure or malfunction, or any and all&#xA;other commercial damages or losses), even if such Contributor&#xA;has been advised of the possibility of such damages.&#xA;&#xA;9. Accepting Warranty or Additional Liability. While redistributing&#xA;the Work or Derivative Works thereof, You may choose to offer,&#xA;and charge a fee for, acceptance of support, warranty, indemnity,&#xA;or other liability obligations and/or rights consistent with this&#xA;License. However, in accepting such obligations, You may act only&#xA;on Your own behalf and on Your sole responsibility, not on behalf&#xA;of any other Contributor, and only if You agree to indemnify,&#xA;defend, and hold each Contributor harmless for any liability&#xA;incurred by, or claims asserted against, such Contributor by reason&#xA;of your accepting any such warranty or additional liability.'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='2'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.group' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='6'>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.source.feature.group' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.doc' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.ui' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'/>
        <required namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.feature.jar' range='[1.3.1.201101032122,1.3.1.201101032122]'>
          <filter>
            (org.eclipse.update.install.features=true)
          </filter>
        </required>
      </requires>
      <touchpoint id='null' version='0.0.0'/>
      <licenses size='1'>
        <license uri='%25licenseURL' url='%25licenseURL'>
          %license
        </license>
      </licenses>
      <copyright>
        %copyright
      </copyright>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='2'>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='MyBatis Generator Eclipse Core Support'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='mybatis.org'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='5'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.callback' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='java.package' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.merge' version='0.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='bundle' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <requires size='5'>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.core' range='1.3.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jdt.core' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.jface.text' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.resources' range='3.6.0'/>
        <required namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.eclipse.core.runtime' range='3.6.0'/>
      </requires>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.1.201101032122)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator Eclipse Core Support Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.1.201101032122'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-ManifestVersion: 2&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.1.201101032122&#xA;Manifest-Version: 1.0&#xA;Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source&#xA;Bundle-Name: %pluginName&#xA;Bundle-Localization: plugin&#xA;Eclipse-SourceBundle: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core;version=&quot;1.3.1.201101032122&quot;;roots:=&quot;.&quot;&#xA;Bundle-Vendor: %providerName
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
    <unit id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521' singleton='false'>
      <update id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' range='[0.0.0,1.3.2.201207161521)' severity='0'/>
      <properties size='5'>
        <property name='df_LT.providerName' value='mybatis.org'/>
        <property name='df_LT.pluginName' value='MyBatis Generator Eclipse Core Support Source'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.name' value='%pluginName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.provider' value='%providerName'/>
        <property name='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.bundle.localization' value='plugin'/>
      </properties>
      <provides size='4'>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.iu' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='osgi.bundle' name='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.eclipse.type' name='source' version='1.0.0'/>
        <provided namespace='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.localization' name='df_LT' version='1.0.0'/>
      </provides>
      <artifacts size='1'>
        <artifact classifier='osgi.bundle' id='org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source' version='1.3.2.201207161521'/>
      </artifacts>
      <touchpoint id='org.eclipse.equinox.p2.osgi' version='1.0.0'/>
      <touchpointData size='1'>
        <instructions size='1'>
          <instruction key='manifest'>
            Bundle-SymbolicName: org.mybatis.generator.eclipse.core.source&#xA;Bundle-Version: 1.3.2.201207161521&#xA;
          </instruction>
        </instructions>
      </touchpointData>
    </unit>
  </units>
</repository>
